Get down tonight
Do a little dance
Make a little love
Get down tonight
(Amy:)Would you like to dance?
(Leonard:)No, thank you.
I'm really not much of a dancer.
(Amy:)You're not exactly winning any trophies
as a conversationalist, either.
(Howard:)I'm sorry.
The bride and groom seem happy.
(Amy:)Why shouldn't they be?
They have a feverish night...
(Amy:)...of socially-approved copulation
ahead of them.
In some cuItures,
we'd stand outside their room...
(Amy:)...cheering as they achieved orgasm.
That sounds like a Iate night,
and I have work in the morning, so...
(Amy:)Leonard, you may not have noticed,
but I am being a delight here.
(Amy:)You're not holding up your end
of the evening.
(Howard:)I'm sorry.
This wedding just reminds me...
...of my kind-of-sort-of girIfriend
9000 miles away.
I have a kind-of-sort-of boyfriend
playing with a model train right now.